Tony Oyola

9428 27th Ave SE, Everett, WA 98208

206.300.7530

tonyoyola86@gmail.com

Objective

Dedicated, motivated and career-minded individual looking to bring over 15 years of solid computer experience, 1 year legitimate game/software testing experience and 5+ years of solid management experience to help enhance workflow efficiency and achieve industry goals.

Skills

Adjusted WPM: 78

Expert proficiency with both PC and Mac-based operating systems **Supervisory experience** of 10+ employees over multiple years

Knowledge of C++, SQL, basic program creation from school and self-taught **Tenacious commitment** to master most challenging work-based objectives **Diligent and meticulous researcher** constantly diving deep to dissect and master

strategies and performance efficiency

Ability to clearly articulate written and/or verbal instructions Well-versed in Google Docs, Microsoft Office, Photoshop Excels in mathematics, technology and written communication

Education

Glendale Community College, Glendale, AZ - Foundational studies toward AAS

Degree

Cascadia Community College, Bothell, WA - Additional requirements in preparation

for transfer toward Software Engineering/Computer Programming

Employment

Superior Services Window Cleaning - Route Manager

07/2019 - Present

Various areas, Washington State

Responsible for managing route with little to no instruction

First employee to contribute to expansion of customer base through new business acquisition

Implemented digital tools to help manage data, such as customer payment, miles and expenses trackers

Managed all business-related expenses and necessary materials

Seattle Shade and Awning - Office Manager

08/2019 - 08/2020

Everett, WA

Responsible for scheduling jobs for multiple crew members

Handled customer communications, including initial contact, price quoting and product information based on customer inquiry

Oversaw employee work schedule, payroll and route planning

Accepted payments, created and managed invoices, accepted product shipments Created a spreadsheet in Excel that streamlined price quotes based on product information entered

Amazon Logistics - Learning Coordinator

04/2016 - 02/2017

Phoenix, AZ

Cover all training responsibilities, including sortation shift and delivery associates

Regularly customized/altered training to better suit station's specific needs Learned Shift Assistant responsibilities and tools to better serve station (COMP, Logistics Internal, Routing Tools, etc)

Helped improve sortation quality with focused training, coaching and improvised stand-up meetings

Created training methods and processes that led to increased metrics in all processes, including sorting, loading and delivery success. These methods would later be adopted in multiple DSPs nationwide

Amazon FBA - Investigation Specialist

06/2015 - 04/2016

Seattle, WA

Experienced SQL based workflow

Minor experience with HTML5

Proficient in 4 queues with up to \$3k approval limit

Became trainer for new-hires after 2 months on the team

Achieved 5 "Just Do Its" in 5 months with the company

Won "Star Pupil" award, 1 of 2 awarded out of 70+ coworkers, after 3 months Regularly requested to complete special projects for upper management

Google (Through Contract) - Team Lead

09/2013 - 06/2015

Bothell, WA

Experience with ARC-GIS, Photoshop, blueprint analysis, team management Became Team Lead after 7 months, over coworkers with more experience. Determined to improve, choosing more difficult projects over simple ones Experience managing team workflow, quality assurance, hiring and training of new hires, setting and meeting goals, both short- and long-term

Quick Ship Electronics Warehouse - Asst. Supervisor Woodinville, WA

Handle all product pickups/deliveries using 26-foot truck

08/2012 - 09/2013

Quickly rose from product tester to assistant floor supervisor in 2 months Responsible for inventory, training, product organization and quality assurance Supervise 10+ employees in product testing, quality assurance and group tasks